Hello! We're on our way to the backstage area because we're at Mellaluna Festival and we're
going to do a fashion show today. Actually two fashion shows. So with all our stuff,
the luggage, making our way there, rehearsals and then showtime and we'll take you along!
That's a glamorous model lifestyle.
I'm surrounded by beautiful people in underwear.
Yeah!
Sorry!
Hello!
We're the colourful people here.
Give us everything you have.
More!
And we want fire, lots of fire, big fire!
Fire up, all at the same time!
Hello, it's me again!
So, we're here at the backstage area.
There's Celine.
All the other persons.
Yeah, you know, I have no idea what I'm gonna do, but we're here, we got ready, now we're waiting for our...
Rehearsal!
Rehearsal! We're gonna wait for our rehearsal.
That's it.
makeup stuff and hair and then we gonna start yeah we go in an all-out food and
then the show starts
I am excited, I think only a few minutes to go and we are all waiting to go on stage.
Woohoo!
United we stand, and we fight to the end, in a world of command, till we're dead but safe from harm.
United we stand, and we fight to the end
In the world of command, till we're dead but safe from harm
Safe from harm
First show is over! How was it? It was great! Did you enjoy it? Yeah I did, how about you?
We had fun, yeah. I think it was fun. We were the best outfits.
And now, food? Food and champagne I guess. First show is done!
That's what the Mongols are doing after the show.
Ignore all our sins
Holy saints we can be
In this fight to be free
Will the sun cease to shine?
Will the planets decline?
Will our worlds be combined?
Leave our solitude behind
Everything is wet, everything is wet underneath.
So sweaty.
We're going to send over the next one for the photoshoot now.
Nothing happened over there.
Cheers!
I think it's fun.
I think our crew is the best because it's just hilarious here with all of us and all
and all the bad jokes and we're looking awesome.
And now we have to do it better, so...
I think it will be even better than the last time.
Always better.
But safe from harm
United we stand
And we fight to the end
In a world of command
Till we're dead
But safe from harm
Safe from harm
Thank you.